312-409-1803 <u>mitesh@mokko.io</u> <u>https://mite.sh</u>

Profile

Empathetic software leader, enthusiastic co-founder, a design fanatic and talented individual software contributor with over 15 years of experience in software engineering across technologies.

Top Skills

NodeJS	ReactJS	React Native	Redux	Express
MongoDB	Next.js	JavaScript	CSS / SCSS	Swift
Unity3D	Sketch	Gatsby	Bootstrap	Bulma

Experience

CTO, ROUTE, INC., CHICAGO, IL - APRIL 2018 - MARCH 2020

Responsible as co-founder for envisioning, building out and maintaining the main SaaS product, as well as pitch the company, help raise funds and recruit / mentor the technical and design team. Oversaw growth from \$0 to \$8k/month; 0 to 100+ paying customers.

UX DESIGNER / FRONTEND ENGINEER (CONTRACT) - ALOGENT – OCTOBER 2019 - MAY 2020

Pitched and delivered a design system for financial services, with a client co-branding focus. Redesigned their entire next generation banking product, along with the creation of rapid prototypes for marketing demos of existing and upcoming features.

FREELANCE / FOUNDING ENGINEER, MOKKO LABS (US & INDIA) - 2016 - CURRENT

Built and delivered several startup MVPs across many stacks; recruited and nurtured a team of talented freelancers in design and development along with the fledgling business in the US and India. At its peak, generated revenues upwards of \$120k per year.

MOBILE SOFTWARE ENGINEER (CONTRACT), SCIENTIFIC GAMES, ALPHARETTA, GA – 2014

Improved and maintained a proprietary mobile SDK built on top of Cordova - specific for contract work in lottery systems and second chance games.

Education

Illinois State University, Normal, Illinois – Bachelor of Science (Major: Computer Science) 2004